questions_easy = [
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Iran?",
        "answers": ["Rasht", "Tehran", "Isfahan", "Mashhad"],
        "correct_answer": "Tehran"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of England?",
        "answers": ["Moscow", "Rome", "Berlin", "London"],
        "correct_answer": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of France?",
        "answers": ["Sen", "Paris", "Horizon", "Reno"],
        "correct_answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Italy?",
        "answers": ["Vatikan", "Sisil", "Rome", "Madrid"],
        "correct_answer": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Germany?",
        "answers": ["Eshtootgart", "Berlin", "Oslo", "Moonikh"],
        "correct_answer": "Berlin"
    }
]

questions_medium = [
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of The USA?",
        "answers": ["Washington DC", "Los Santos :D", "Los Angeles", "California"],
        "correct_answer": "Washington DC"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Canada?",
        "answers": ["Ottawa", "Toronto", "Montreal", "Virginia"],
        "correct_answer": "Ottawa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Australia?",
        "answers": ["Canberra", "Sydney", "Melbourne", "Packitow"],
        "correct_answer": "Canberra"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Austria?",
        "answers": ["Vienna", "Budapest", "Prauge", "Oslo"],
        "correct_answer": "Vienna"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Argentina?",
        "answers": ["Rashina", "Rio", "Arginia", "Boines Aires"],
        "correct_answer": "Boines Aires"
    }
]

questions_hard = [
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of The Togo?",
        "answers": ["Kinshasa", "Karafia", "Lomé", "Barticia"],
        "correct_answer": "Lomé"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Niger?",
        "answers": ["Abuja", "Niamey", "Lome", "Harare"],
        "correct_answer": "Niamey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of South Aferica?",
        "answers": ["Pretoria", "Cape Town", "Bloemfontein", "All of them"],
        "correct_answer": "All of them"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Philippines?",
        "answers": ["Manila", "Varsu", "Prauge", "Adiss Ababa"],
        "correct_answer": "Manila"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is The Capital of Trinidad and Tobago?",
        "answers": ["Rojandi", "Rio", "Port of Spain", "Port of Madrid"],
        "correct_answer": "Port of Spain"
    }
]




